JONATHAN SANTOSO



CONTACT INFORMATION

- jonathansantoso020@gmail.com
- Building 431 Cnr Beazley Avenue &, University Bvd, Bentley WA 6102, Australia
- 0416403411

SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Ouick Learner

LANGUAGES

- Indonesian | Native
- English | Advanced
- Malay | Intermediate

PROFILE

I'm a 20-year-old Indonesian international student from Curtin University looking to build experience and gain skill to work in the real world. I have customer service skills I learned from my previous jobs as a waiter and retail staff. My greatest strengths are creativity and problem solving which can help the company tackle problems that may present itself. I'm a Hard worker that can provide more energy and work for the company. I'm very willing to put effort into learning to be better at the job that I'm assigned to. I also love to work in a team and willing to communicate which would help to create a better team chemistry and working environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WAITER

Miso Hangry. South Perth | Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

- ' Greeting, serving, and taking orders from customers.
- · Cleaning the store and dishes.
- ' Help make the salad for the dishes.
- Organizing the store and its products to make it look neater and more accessible for customers.
- Answering the store phone which is usually inquiries regarding the store from customer.

DAIRY RETAIL STAFF

Coles. Karawara | Jul 2024 - Aug 2024

- Restocking the shelves in the dairy section.
- Organizing the product to make it neater and more accessible for customers.
- · Helping customers find items that are related to the dairy section.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE, ECONOMICS MAJOR

Curtin University. Bentley, WA, Australia | Feb 2022 - Present

DIPLOMA OF BUSINESS AND COMMERCE

Curtin College. Bentley, WA, Austalia | Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

INDONESIAN HIGHSCHOOL DIPLOMA

SMANI Tanjungpandan.

JI. Gatot Subroto, Tanjungpandan, Belitung | Jul 2017 - Jul 2020 Achievements during this period:

- 2nd place in Tanjungpandan city Smansa Cup U18 boys basketball tournament during junior year.
- $^{\circ}$ 2nd place in Tanjungpandan city Smansa Cup U18 boys basketball tournament during senior year.
- 2nd place in Belitung regency Dispora Cup U18 boys basketball tournament during senior year.
- Got picked to play for the Belitung regency U21 basketball team during junior year to compete in a provincial level tournament.
- Got picked to play for the Belitung regency U15 basketball team during freshman year to compete in a provincial level tournament.